[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
Let's get started, shall we?
Let's go all out!
And have fun.
Salud,
amigos.
FLEX X COP 2
[♪ upbeat classical guitar music playing]
[singing in Spanish]
[vocalizing a mariachi holler]
Damn it, what the hell
are these bastards doing?
So damn loud.
Hey, just tip them so they'll go away.
With what money?
You think I have money?
[mariachero] Huh?
You don't have any money?
[scoffs]
Your victims lost 100 billion won,
so how do you not have any money?
Who the hell are you assholes?
Gangha Violent Crime Investigation Team 1.
-[scoffs]
-[both chuckle]
Jeez.
You followed us all the way here?
[mariachero] Exactly. Why did I
have to come all the way here?
Because of you guys,
I rented this entire place
and even flew in
on a private jet, you assholes.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[men grunting]
[discordant accordion note playing]
[grunts, groans]
[both grunting]
[grunting continues]
[blade swishing]
[groans]
[grunting]
-[discordant accordion note plays]
-[grunts]
[groans]
-[groans]
[grunting]
STYLE
::cue()
[grunts heavily]
[heavy thud]
-[blade swishes]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
-[exclaims]
-[thuds]
[coughing]
[shattering]
[exclaims]
[groans, grunting]
-[blade swishes]
-[grunting]
[yelps]
[screams]
[thuds]
[drumbeats resonating]
[blade swishes]
[drum thuds]
-[blade swishes]
-[grunts]
[groans]
[knife whooshes]
-[exclaiming in pain]
-[joint cracks]
[exclaims, grunts]
[both grunting]
Huh. Ha-ha!
[♪ dramatic music continues]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
-[blade swishes]
-[all grunting]
[groans]
[grunting]
Out of the way!
-[groans]
-[thuds]
[grunts]
[♪ dramatic music fades]
[men groaning]
God damn it.
-[gunshot]
-[patrons screaming]
[♪ tense music playing]
You want to die?
[laughs maliciously]
[panting]
[maracas rattle]
-What the hell?
-[doors open]
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
Hmm...
Shit.
[sighs]
[vocalizing]
-Bang!
-Jeez!
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music fades]
NORTH MEXICO AERONAUTICAL CENTER
[sighs contentedly]
[in Spanish] That was
an impressive operation, Flex Cop.
[in Spanish] Thank you very much.
[narrator, in Korean]
Next week's Specialist
is a third-generation billionaire heir
and violent crimes detective,
Senior Inspector Jin Isoo.
He recently arrested members
of a pyramid scheme ring in Mexico.
Detective Jin joined the police through
a special recruitment program for lawyers
and has since built an impressive career.
He uncovered the dark secrets
of a powerful business family,
solved the murder case
of artist Noh Youngjae,
and held an exhibition for the painter
who died after being gravely wronged.
He caught the killers
who preyed on the elderly
and retrieved the long-lost national seal,
which he donated to the state.
Don't miss next week's episode
on Flex Cop Senior Inspector Jin Isoo.
SPECIALIST
FLEX X COP SENIOR INSPECTOR JIN ISOO
STYLE
::cue()
NUMBER 1 SAFETY!! NUMBER 1 PUBLIC ORDER!!
GANGHA POLICE STATION
[tires screech]
[engine roaring]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Ah. You're here early. Hello.
-The weather's lovely today--
-[director] Cut.
KANG JAEEUN - JANG HYEONWOO
You don't need to say hello.
Just do what you'd normally do.
Let's try that again.
-[camera lens whirs]
-Got it.
-We're going again.
-[car door closes]
[camera lens whirs]
All right, come on in.
Ah, the best veteran detective
of the Violent Crime Investigation Team 1
and my right-hand man,
Inspector Park Junyoung.
VIOLENT CRIME INVESTIGATION TEAM 1
INSPECTOR PARK JUNYOUNG
The golden rookie of Team 1
and my left-hand man,
Senior Police Officer Choi Kyungjin.
[clears throat] Hello.
SENIOR POLICE OFFICER CHOI KYUNGJIN
Huh? Dr. Yoon?
Come in.
And that is
the NFS's best forensic pathologist,
Dr. Yoon Jiwon.
NFS FORENSIC PATHOLOGIST
DR. YOON JIWON
Why is she here?
Go ahead. You can pass through.
I think she came on purpose.
-This is Violent Crime...
-Ah!
These well-dressed folks here
are Violent Crime Investigation Team 2.
[chuckles]
-Got a wedding to go to?
-No, no.
[both chuckle]
VIOLENT CRIME INVESTIGATION TEAM 2
[Isoo] Now, don't block the camera.
Move aside.
Move aside. Huh. Oh.
That's our team leader's desk.
She went to LA on a training program.
I don't know who our new leader will be,
but I'm here waiting for you,
so please come join us.
My desk is over there.
[sighs contentedly]
Oh, this. As you know,
I joined through the lawyer track.
So I went to the police academy
and graduated top of my class again.
I just don't seem to know
how to be average. Huh.
And this.
[sighs contentedly] I made this
so that anyone can report anything,
and no crime goes undetected.
But nothing big has been reported so far.
Just missing dog reports.
What am I, John Wick?
MESSAGES
Oh, this one looks interesting.
Let's see.
[distorted voice] Detective Jin.
Let the game begin.
What's this?
[computer chimes]
-I have a gift for you.
-Huh?
This looks suspicious.
Right?
Detective Park, come see this.
What is it this time?
Oh. This is Hansu Department Store.
It's ours?
STYLE
::cue()
Yes, I saw that
when I went there with my girlfriend.
It might be another prank.
Right.
People send all kinds of messages here.
Let's go check it out.
It's not like we have
any usable footage right now.
Then, shall we? Huh?
Let's move out!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-Come on.
-Let's move out! Mmm!
[sighs]
Looks like we've got ourselves
a most interesting case.
Detective Park, you drive.
Cut. We're moving out too.
Let's move out.
[music increases in tempo]
[excited chatter]
-Bro, this is it.
-[Isoo] Huh.
Yeah? Give it here, Detective Choi.
I don't get what we're doing here.
They're filming.
[♪ tense music playing]
[sighs]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey.
[distorted voice] You found it quickly.
Are we being watched right now?
-[cell phone vibrating]
-[in English] Hint.
Hmm...
[cell phone vibrating]
[in Korean] A priest.
A box, hash D... What is this?
It's a Hex color code.
Tan.
TAN
I have a bad feeling about this.
[♪ tense music continues]
[Junyoung] What goes inside
the parentheses?
Width?
Or height?
Tan color. Tan.
Hey.
[inhales sharply] I think it's this.
Width, height, or...
Breadth?
Bomb?
Homemade.
-Homemade bomb.
Don't touch that!
-[clicks]
-[beeping]
-[Kyungjin] Bro!
-What?
Don't move. Stay still.
[Isoo] Why? What is it?
Just hold still.
Why? What's wrong?
I told you not to touch it.
[beeping continues]
This is a bomb.
You should've told me sooner!
Zoom in.
[softly] What do I do?
Stop filming.
God, what do I do?
STYLE
::cue()
[alarm ringing]
[PA announcement] A security threat
has been detected in the building.
All customers,
please evacuate immediately.
[officer] Slowly, please!
To the left, please.
As fast as you safely can.
Please exit in an orderly manner.
[PA announcement] A security threat
has been detected in the building.
All customers,
please evacuate immediately.
Shouldn't we be leaving too?
It's not safe, so you guys should go too.
Okay. Let's pack it up.
[nervously] Pack it up.
[Jaeeun] Quickly.
[Isoo grunts]
[line ringing]
Chief.
Please send in the bomb squad.
Yes. Okay.
[grunts in frustration]
Bro, don't worry.
The bomb squad's on the way.
That's not it.
-My leg's killing me.
-Your leg?
Let me massage it.
-No, the right leg.
-The other one.
Here? Down below?
-Now, the left.
-The left.
-[Kyungjin] Down below?
-[Isoo] Yeah, down below.
[inhales sharply]
[Jaeeun] Do you have a clear shot?
Yes, a really clear shot.
Shouldn't we be evacuating?
You want to pass up
an opportunity like this?
Some people even go into war zones.
Get your act together.
[police sirens approaching]
SPECIAL OPERATIONS UNIT
This way.
-It's right here.
-[Isoo] Over here.
[SOU lead] Step back.
Run an X-ray.
Don't move if you want to live.
DANGER
[device rapidly beeping]
[grunts softly]
[digital beep]
[SOU lead] Explosive confirmed.
There's a pressure plate under the device.
We'll disarm it here.
[♪ tense music playing]
Shh... [groans nervously]
What do I do? How do we...
[♪ suspenseful music intensifies]
Is it done?
-Is it done?
-No.
It'll detonate in 10 seconds.
Huh?
[SOU lead] On three,
run back as fast as you can.
-What?
-[SOU lead] Three.
-Can I let go?
-[SOU lead] Two.
-Bro.
-Do I let go?
-[SOU lead] One.
-Bro, run!
[panting]
[SOU lead chuckling]
Why didn't it go off?
[SOU lead] Device rendered safe.
Hey, nutjob.
I told you to stay out of trouble.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ upbeat music playing]
-Instructor Joo Hyera?
-[chuckles]
NATIONAL POLICE COUNTERTERRORISM TEAM
TEAM LEADER JOO HYERA
[exhales sharply]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[upbeat music stops]
[Hyera] Did someone kill your dog?
You think you're John Wick?
Are you Keanu Reeves?
I was just...
[Hyera] Listen up.
You are issued firearms
to protect the public.
Use it only as a last resort,
and use it as safely as possible.
We just have to hit the target, don't we?
So you're the nutjob of this class.
[exhales softly]
[target pulley whirring]
[Isoo sighs]
[in English] My name is John Wick.
[sighs contentedly]
[in Korean] Looks like
a civilian passing by got hit.
-What are you going to do about it?
-Huh?
[Hyera] Eyes forward.
[groans]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
-Stand straight.
-[sighs softly]
Both hands on the gun.
Go sit down.
[sighs]
Shall we try someone tall this time?
Any volunteers?
I'll do it.
[recruits] Ooh!
Jin Isoo, come on up.
-Let's do this!
-[recruits cheering]
Don't come crying even if you get hurt.
All right. Come at me.
[yells]
Oh.
[groans]
You're not crying, are you?
[exhales sharply]
[training officer] You're doing great.
You're almost there.
Hey, nutjob!
You're abandoning your teammates?
[whistle blows]
-Defensive position!
-[recruits] Defensive position!
Advance!
[grunting]
[exclaims]
[grunts]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screeching]
[tires screeching]
Hey, nutjob!
[tires screech]
Back to start!
-[whistle blows]
-[Isoo] Seven, eight, nine.
[whistle blows]
Hey, nutjob. Do it properly.
-Jeez, I lost count.
-[whistle blows]
[whistle blows rhythmically]
[whistle echoes]
[Isoo] That instructor from hell...
It's her?
But she's with Counterterrorism.
She was filling in
for an instructor on sick leave.
She hates me.
[sighs wearily]
God, the trauma. [sighs]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
SPECIALIST
-[Isoo] My leg's killing me.
-[Kyungjin] Your leg? Let me massage it.
-[Isoo] No, the right leg.
-[Kyungjin] The other one.
[grunts on screen]
-[Kyungjin] Here? Down below?
-[Isoo] Now, the left.
[Kyungjin] The left.
-[Kyungjin] Down below?
-[Isoo] Yeah, down below.
We can't use this clip of Jin Isoo.
He looks like an idiot.
-Then what do we do?
-[keyboard clacks]
[sighs in exasperation]
But this is such a great story.
[keyboard clacks]
[♪ quirky music playing]
Hey.
Send the footage of Jin Isoo
to the news team.
But what about our story?
[keyboard clacks]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[news anchor 1] Earlier today,
a homemade bomb was discovered
at Hansu Department Store.
The billionaire heir
and detective of Gangha Police Station,
Detective Jin Isoo,
discovered the explosive.
[news anchor 2] He seems frozen
in the footage. What transpired?
[news anchor 1] Detective Jin didn't know
it was a bomb
and triggered it by accident.
[news anchor 2] And why is he reacting
like that? The bomb didn't even go off.
If you look at the footage--
[sighs in exasperation]
-Chief Park.
-Yes, sir.
I didn't want to come here.
Because of Jin Isoo.
If I'd had another option,
I wouldn't be here.
Yes, sir.
The head of the police station retired,
and his team leader went abroad,
so what is he still doing here?
He's a chaebol heir.
He should be running the company
or off somewhere enjoying himself.
So why?
Because he's a detective.
I hate to admit it,
but Jin Isoo is a good detective.
Right, he's a good detective,
so he's earned himself
two excessive force complaints
and three civil lawsuits.
[chuckles] These were all cleared, sir.
Chief Park.
Come to your senses.
He's nothing but trouble for our station.
I've been here less than a month,
and he's already screwed up.
What are you going to do?
The Counterterrorism Team
will assess the bomb
and work with
the Violent Crime Investigation Team 1.
The Cybercrime Team
is tracking down who sent the DM.
[sighs] God, I...
Why haven't you found them
a new team leader?
Because no one wants the job.
See?
Who'd want to manage
a rich kid who was handed the job?
Huh?
I'll keep looking, sir.
Just focus on the investigation.
Go catch the guy!
Yes, sir.
[sighs in exasperation]
[news anchor 1] Earlier today,
a homemade bomb was discovered
at Hansu Department Store.
The billionaire heir
and detective of Gangha Police Station,
Detective Jin Isoo,
discovered the explosive...
[groans] My leg's numb.
I can't bear it anymore!
You can't.
It'll go off if you move!
[news anchor 2] And why is he
reacting like that?
The bomb didn't even go off.
-Three minutes.
-Thanks.
[Byungsik, in English] Okay.
[in Korean] Turn the TV off!
We're on duty.
-That's not funny.
-Bro!
VIOLENT CRIME INVESTIGATION TEAM 1
PARK JUNYOUNG
I told you not to make fun of him.
[chuckles softly]
How could I not? It's too entertaining.
This one's good for 10 years.
MR. CHOI
INCOMING CALL
[cell phone ringing through car audio]
Hi, Mr. Choi.
Detective Jin.
What happened? Are you all right?
I'm not all right.
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
[sighs]
As long as you weren't hurt.
There's nothing wrong
with being embarrassed.
[Isoo sighs]
You're the great Jin Isoo.
Are you really going to let this
get to you?
He's right, bro. Cheer up.
You guys didn't make the news.
The most humiliating moment
of my life is on TV right now.
Come on, bro. People will forget about it.
Forget? They won't forget.
This'll last a decade.
Then again, your ex slapping you
on Gangnam-daero was four years ago.
Is that still going around?
Then this might last forever.
[gasps]
You should just carve it
into your tombstone.
"The man who triggered a bomb."
[laughing]
Bro.
-Hey, where are you going?
-Bro.
-Hey, Bomb Guy.
-Bro!
[Junyoung] Wait up!
Bomb Guy.
-Come on.
-Bro.
How many times is this now?
-Also...
-You're laughing?
You're seriously laughing right now?
Sorry.
The news team kept begging us,
saying it was a huge scoop.
-Sorry.
Even so, you made me look
like a complete idiot.
STYLE
::cue()
In that kind of situation,
anyone would have looked like an idiot.
Are you mocking me right now?
Or are you trying to rub it in?
Which is it?
She's coming. Let's go.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
They've moved on to her, haven't they?
Well, she is pretty cool.
I'm a fan too now.
Are you moving on to her too?
-We'll see.
-"We'll see"?
"We'll see"?
That little...
Hang in there, nutjob.
What the...
This is ridiculous.
Ugh. My head hurts.
Jeez.
[sighs]
[♪ quirky music playing]
PRIEST, BREADTH, TAN (HEX CODE)
PHOTO EVIDENCE 3, BOMB X-RAY
HANSU DEPARTMENT STORE
ATTEMPTED BOMBING
The bomb appears to have been made
with ammonium nitrate.
It's a simple design.
It detonates when the button
is pressed and then released.
A bomb design like this
is all over the dark web.
Which means it will be difficult
to identify a suspect.
Anything on your end?
Right, we checked
all the security cameras in the building,
but there's too much foot traffic,
and the cameras are too far away
to identify the suspect.
The account that sent the DM was fake too.
I'm sure it was.
No fingerprints were found on the device.
Based on our analysis,
there wasn't much ammonium nitrate.
Even if it had gone off, the blast radius
would've been about a meter.
In other words, it wasn't much of a bomb.
Right? Okay.
If we hadn't defused it in time,
you would've lost your hands.
Think before you start touching things.
If I'd known it was a bomb,
I wouldn't have touched it.
Why didn't you know?
You were given all the clues.
What're you looking at?
Ma'am, we came up
with a whole new concept.
There's no need for that.
I'm not going to go on camera.
Please delete everything you filmed today.
But if you were in it,
it'd help the police's image.
I don't have time,
and I don't want my face out there.
Please delete the footage.
What do we do?
We have nothing for next week's show.
I know.
I said, I know.
[sighs] This reminds me of that saying,
"Better the devil you know." [sighs]
The ship's sailed. Now you're in trouble.
[clicking tongue] Bet you miss me now.
What?
[door opens]
[door closes]
Hey, Joo.
Sir.
It's been a while.
[chuckles] It has.
Coffee?
-[chuckles]
-How have you been?
Oh. Same old, same old.
I miss being out in the field.
I heard you've been doing great
over there in SOU.
[chuckling]
-It's all thanks to you.
-So you do know.
[both chuckle]
How does it feel to be back here?
It really takes me back.
Gangha is like home to me.
Guess I'll be seeing you around.
Yes.
My team is going to work here for a while.
Detective Jin Isoo needs protection too.
Sure. Team 1 doesn't have
a leader right now,
so I'll leave the case in your hands.
All right.
It might just be a prank,
but someone
could actually be after Jin Isoo.
I know.
You need to catch the suspect quickly.
Got it.
[sighs]
Can I let go? Do I let go?
[Kyungjin] Bro, run!
[Hyera] Hey, nutjob.
I told you to stay out of trouble.
[♪ upbeat hip-hop music playing]
Eyes forward.
You're not crying, are you?
[Isoo] That instructor from hell...
[Kyungjin] It's her?
Hey, nutjob!
Think before you start touching things.
STYLE
::cue()
[cell phone vibrates]
[Hyeonwoo] Please forgive us
and answer your phone.
[Jaeeun] We weren't thinking straight.
[cell phone vibrating]
SBC DIRECTOR KANG JAEEUN
Jeez.
[sighs] Why are you being so clingy? Huh?
Well, I do have an event today
that would make for good content.
Okay, fine. Then write up a new contract.
Nothing goes on air
until I've seen the final edit.
Okay. Bye.
[line disconnects]
We're leading
this investigation as of today.
We don't need any desks.
We'll use the conference table.
She thinks she's some big-shot
team leader, doesn't she?
-I'm heading out first. Dress sharp.
-[Junyoung] Okay.
Detective Jin, where are you going?
I have a launch event today.
-A launch event?
-For a whiskey I developed.
Don't you know moonlighting's prohibited?
I started it four years ago
but quit when I became a cop.
Don't go.
What?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-But I'm the star of the event.
-Then push it back.
[scoffs]
[sighs deeply]
Do I still look like
a recruit to you? Huh?
Is that an order?
I've been assigned to lead this case.
Didn't you get the memo?
I did.
We still haven't identified
a bombing suspect.
They might be after you.
It's probably a prank.
They even gave us clues.
It was just to humiliate me,
and it was a huge success thanks to you.
Besides, I've always had
people out to kill me.
Why?
Just, you know,
for petty reasons.
All the more reason to be careful.
Don't go.
My security team
is checking every box, so just let it go.
I'll handle it, okay?
See you guys later.
[sighs softly]
-[door closes]
-[clears throat]
We will
keep an eye on him.
Right.
We'll watch over him.
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
[♪ elegant piano music playing]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[crowd cheering]
-Jin Isoo!
[in English] Cheers.
-Cheers!
[exhales contentedly]
Bang!
[giggles]
Oh?
Kwaktube.
[in Korean] I thought
you'd be too busy to come.
-No way.
-You're looking good.
Oh, come on.
By the way,
isn't your wife due soon?
She's actually due tomorrow.
[gasps]
[cell phone vibrating]
-The hospital...
-The hospital?
Hello?
Yes. What?
I need to go right now.
Right now?
The baby's coming.
The baby...
Good luck!
[sighs] Hope the baby
doesn't take after the dad.
Ah. I'm the one who made this.
The logo is the defining feature,
you get...
Hold on.
[sighs] Clothes do make the man.
What?
[in English] Oh, oh. Stop.
[in Korean] What are you doing here?
I didn't invite you.
I'm going to check inside.
There's no need. You're embarrassing me.
You can't be here dressed like that.
Ever heard of a dress code?
You two, head inside.
Go.
Security.
Get her out of here, okay?
Dress code violation.
-Hey, Jin Isoo.
-Let's go.
Wait, Jin Isoo... [sighs]
[exclaims] That damn nutjob.
What happened?
It's nothing.
Keep watch.
[♪ smooth jazz music playing]
[Isoo] Mmm.
Oh, this smells great.
Right? There's a subtle hint of vanilla.
Try it. Cheers.
[glasses clink]
I'll drink it later, just in case.
Me too. We need to protect you.
I told you, it's fine.
I don't need protecting. [sighs]
Oh...
That's what your job does to you.
She can't switch off.
[scoffs]
[sighs] Whatever. Just ignore her.
STYLE
::cue()
See? I told you nothing would happen.
You guys didn't get a taste,
so I'll send you a whole box.
Awesome.
[Jaeeun] Thanks for today.
I'll call you after we're done editing.
Make sure I look cool, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
Oh, no.
Guess you couldn't find the bomb.
Have a drink before you go.
-No.
-[Isoo] Suit yourself.
You're going home, right?
Where do you live?
[scoffs]
Noblesse.
Don't wander around. Go straight home.
-[sighs in exasperation]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[distorted voice] Detective Jin,
did you think the game was over?
Round 2.
[♪ intense music playing]
What on earth?
[glass shattering]
[Isoo breathing heavily]
[Hyera whimpering]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. You?
[Junyoung] Kyungjin, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[indistinct conversation]
[♪ tense music continues]
-[sighs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[distorted voice] Detective Jin,
you got lucky.
[disembodied malicious laughter]
[news anchor] Another homemade bomb attack
has occurred in the heart of Seoul.
Once again, Detective Jin Isoo
was at the center of the attack,
as the attack took place at a venue
where he was hosting an event.
Police say the suspect's motive
remains unknown.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[Junyoung] Thank you for your cooperation.
Did you get the full staff and guest list?
Yes, they just faxed it over.
And the list of YouTubers?
They'll check and send it over.
Check the security footage
and identify anyone suspicious.
-Got it.
-[Junyoung] Got it.
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs] It's out of the camera's view.
-[Junyoung] Is this all the footage?
-Yes.
I'll check around the building.
You chase the YouTubers for their footage.
Got it.
[distorted voice] Detective Jin.
Let the game begin.
[glass shattering]
I have a gift for you.
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[device beeping]
-Don't touch that!
-[Kyungjin] Bro!
[distorted voice] Did you think
the game was over?
Detective Jin, you got lucky.
[tinkling]
[high-pitched ringing swells]
-[high-pitched ringing stops]
-[gasps, panting]
Are you okay?
[panting heavily]
So...
Is someone trying to kill you?
You should stop filming now.
But we signed a contract.
You are no longer allowed in this office.
Please leave.
[breath trembles]
Detective Jin, a word?
[♪ tense music playing]
Write up a list of people
who might want to kill you.
I didn't mean that literally.
No one actually wants me dead.
Doesn't matter how trivial.
Write down anyone who hates you
or anyone you've hurt.
Everyone you can think of.
It doesn't take much to hold a grudge.
[sighs]
Jin Isoo.
Using a homemade bomb
means they have nothing to lose.
They don't care if they die.
That's how determined they are
to kill you.
A pager was used
in the Seongje bombing three years ago.
That's right.
Ask for the file.
He should be out of prison by now.
Yes, ma'am.
[Kyungjin] I got the footage
from the YouTubers.
[mouse clicks]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[keyboard clacks]
He seems suspicious.
-Wait.
-[keyboard clacks]
NOH JINSU, AGE 27
-It's him. Noh Jinsu, age 27.
-Right.
[keyboard clacking]
IDENTITY SEARCH
NOH JINSU
His father worked at Hansu Chemical
and left eight months ago.
-What's his address?
-17-38 Yongpae-dong.
-Let's go.
-[Kyungjin] Okay.
[officer] I checked the Seongje bombing.
Park Gyeongtae has indeed been released.
Let's go check him out.
-Yes, ma'am.
We identified a suspicious waiter.
We're going to see someone
who built a similar bomb.
We'll go check on the waiter.
Okay. I'll send my team as backup.
Be careful.
-Got it.
STYLE
::cue()
[pen clicks]
I should've killed you on that day.
Shut up!
[both grunting]
I'll take away everything you have.
[pen clicks]
[Isoo] Never die.
Live forever, haunted by regret.
-[pen clicks]
-[door opens]
Mr. Choi.
Are you all right?
Not really.
I've been told to find someone
who wants to kill me,
but I can only think of one person
who would want to kill me
and actually be capable of it.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
SPECIAL OPERATIONS UNIT
[♪ foreboding music continues]
[beaker clinks]
Keep quiet and stand by.
[loud knocking]
You have a visitor.
It's your brother,
Jin Isoo.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
STYLE
::cue()
[rattles, clatters]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
Park Gyeongtae, don't move.
Turn around slowly.
Noh Jinsu!
What's all this?
[♪ foreboding music continues]
[gasps]
-Who are you?
-Police.
-[whirring]
-[Gyeongtae] That thing...
It'll blow if we leave it.
-[gun cocks]
-Don't move.
-[dial clicks]
-[whirring stops]
[sniffles]
Is that your next bomb?
No.
It's fertilizer for the future of farming.
Yes, fertilizer.
But it's also used to make bombs.
This is what caused
the explosion in Lebanon.
You made this, didn't you?
[Gyeongtae] Ah...
Ah, that.
It's been all over the Internet
for three years now.
I've already served my time.
I don't do that anymore.
I set it off back then
because of that jerk I worked for.
Lately,
I've been using my brain for other things.
INVENTION COMPETITION
[♪ music swells, fades]
AWARD CERTIFICATE
[Jinsu] A bomb?
[spluttering] It wasn't me.
Then what were you doing?
[exhales deeply]
It's really nothing big.
-You're Jin Isoo's stalker, right?
-Huh?
Were you so obsessed
you wanted to kill him?
We'll talk at the station.
[spluttering]
It's a talisman.
What?
People still make bombs like this?
But it'll be tough to catch them.
[chuckles] That's easy to make.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
The shaman told me
to leave it beside the person
I want to become,
and then I'd receive divine revelation
and make a lot of money like Jin Isoo.
But then it actually blew up.
STYLE
::cue()
Isn't that amazing?
What was inside it?
Well...
My fingernails, some hair,
and the paper talisman.
Then why did your father leave his job?
Wasn't he forced to resign?
My dad?
He moved to the countryside
to take up farming.
He grows persimmons.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
[♪ gentle poignant music playing]
I'm not here to check in on you.
Right.
Someone's trying to kill me.
What?
Someone's trying to kill me with a bomb.
Who?
Yeah.
Who could it be?
No matter how much I think about it,
you're the only one I can think of.
I have a lot of time here.
So...
I keep thinking
about what a fool I've been.
I wrote you a letter.
Several times.
I made excuses
and asked for forgiveness.
But I couldn't bring myself to send it.
Because I don't deserve to be forgiven.
[sighs]
Isoo.
It's not me.
My biggest regret
is hurting you.
Hurting me?
[scoffs]
No.
You ruined my life.
It probably isn't revenge.
The Isoo I know...
would never make someone
want revenge this badly.
It might be...
driven by desire.
[door opens]
[door slams]
Isoo.
STYLE
::cue()
[Mr. Choi] Will you be all right?
I think you should go somewhere safe.
I'll be fine.
This is a police station.
-[chuckles softly]
-[door opens]
Call me if you need anything.
Bye.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ pensive music playing]
TARGET BELIEVED TO BE JIN ISOO
I put a surveillance team
on Park Gyeongtae.
We're also tracing his bank accounts.
So anyone can make that kind of bomb,
not just Park Gyeongtae?
Yes. What about the waiter?
He just idolizes Jin Isoo.
[sighs]
Where have you been?
I had somewhere to go.
Don't you get it?
Someone's after you.
I know.
That's why I went to see him.
The one person who wants to kill me.
Who?
My brother.
He...
[Hyera] I know. You don't need to explain.
So?
You think it's him?
He's never had any visitors.
He even refused to see his lawyer.
We're still monitoring Park Gyeongtae,
but we're unable to identify
a suspect at this point.
-[sighs]
-For now, I think we should move
Detective Jin to a safe house.
-A safe house?
-Yes.
We'll take him to one of the safe houses
secured by the Counterterrorism Team.
Where is it?
Sorry, sir,
but I can't share that information.
What?
There could be someone
in the station with a grudge.
Are you saying
the culprit could be one of our own?
-Sir.
-[Hyera] It's just a precaution.
Just to be safe.
[exhales in disbelief]
All this trouble
just because of one rich kid.
Safe house or wherever,
just get him out of here.
-Before something goes wrong.
-Yes, sir.
Put Team 1 with him. You can trust them.
Yes, I'll do that.
Detective Jin Isoo,
you'll be moving to a safe house.
We're leaving now. Quietly.
Team 1 will join you.
Where exactly are we going?
I'll tell you on the way.
Give me a break.
I just need to stay holed up at home.
I'm not going.
We don't have a suspect,
and your place isn't safe either.
You're a target now.
You don't get to decide.
[sighs wearily]
[car alarm chirps]
Get in this one.
I can't just ride in any car. [scoffs]
You want to make it obvious
Jin Isoo is in that car?
STYLE
::cue()
Get in.
[muttering] Who does she think she is,
my boss?
Get in.
[♪ ominous music plays]
[Kyungjin] Maybe I should've gotten
in that car.
I don't think we should leave them alone.
I'm sure they won't fight.
They're not kids.
Nutjob, you asleep?
What do you want now?
There's no need to be scared.
Nothing bad will happen.
We'll catch them while you're there.
You think I'm an idiot or something?
I'm a cop too.
[chuckles softly]
Why are you even a cop?
Picking a fight with me again?
No, I'm just curious.
You're incredibly rich,
and you can do whatever you want.
Then what about you?
If you were incredibly rich,
would you quit?
-No.
-Same with me.
I've tried and done it all,
but this is my calling.
What?
Run out of fights to pick?
[scoffs]
You sure are different.
Says the person
who's been calling me a nutjob.
[vibrating]
Just answer your phone.
It's not me.
[vibrating continues]
It's not me either.
What's that?
It's a box I've never seen before.
What are you doing?
That red light on the box...
[vibrating continues]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[timer beeping]
-It's a bomb.
-What?
It's a bomb!
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense music playing]
[car horns blaring]
What's going on?
There's a bomb in the car.
Blast radius is 50... No, 100 meters.
Take the wheel.
[inhales sharply, mutters indistinctly]
[tires screeching]
Four minutes left.
[tires screech]
[exhales sharply]
-[timer beeping]
-[Isoo mutters indistinctly]
[engine revving]
GANGHA QUAY
I know a place.
[tires screeching]
-[car horn blares]
-[tires screech]
STYLE
::cue()
Wait, stop!
-[car horn honking]
-[siren blaring]
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense music playing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[Hyera] There are people here. Be careful.
[car horn honking]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
Detective Park, stop!
[tires screech]
[siren blaring distantly]
-Nine seconds.
-Open the door.
-What?
-Open the door!
[suspenseful music intensifies]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 1
SERIAL BOMBING ATTACKS BEGIN...
WHO IS AFTER JIN ISOO?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Special Cast.
Kwak Siyang, Kwaktube, Bae Seongjae
-[cell phone vibrates]
-[distorted voice] Come alone.
He'll blow up if I see anyone else.
-[Isoo] Mr. Choi!
-[Hyeonwoo] I got a DM.
-I was told to come here and film you die.
-Detective!
-[Hyera] I think Jin Isoo has been set up.
-[explosion]
I don't know how far ahead they planned.
Whose idea was it
to do a feature on Detective Jin Isoo?
[in English] Action.
[Isoo, in Korean] I think I know
what the bombers are after.
-[Kyungjin] Isoo disappeared.
-Detective Jin!
We need a different location.
-Is this Joo Hyera's place?
-The bomber would never expect it.
I didn't expect it either.
I'm going to a hotel.
Once Jin Isoo leaves,
I'd like to pick his replacement.
[Isoo] No way. Is someone...
[Hyera] It sent Jin Isoo to a safe house
and isolated him.
[Isoo] That bastard was bluffing.
[narrator, on TV] Next week's Specialist
is a third-generation billionaire heir
and violent crimes detective,
Senior Inspector Jin Isoo.
He recently arrested members
of a pyramid scheme ring in Mexico.
Detective Jin joined the police through
a special recruitment program for lawyers
-and has since built an impressive career.
-[sighs] That nutjob.
Don't miss next week's episode
on Flex Cop Senior Inspector Jin Isoo.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee